

SAMEER AIJAZ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am 21 years old and acheiving the dream to create something big.I am Full Stack web developer.I started my career after college and I am currently doing my bachelors from SMI University in SE. My stacks are MERN stack and MEVN Stack.

EDUCATION

2021-2024 SMI university. BS(SE).

2018-2020
Bahria Foundation College.
Intermediate.
Computer Science.

2004-2017 Sir Syed Children's Academy. Matriculation.

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

JAMAL BROTHERS. | 2022-present Dimensional System. | 2022-2022 ASASA TECH. | 2018-2021

- Created web applications using MERN and MEVN stack.
- I used Tailwind css and bootstrap css as CSS framework.
- I used express as nodejs framework.

CONTACT ME

- +92 311 4672433
- aijazsameer5@gmail.com
- www.sameeraijaz.com
- B 6/ 4 Pakcolony Mangopir road Karachi

